OK, let's continue.
And grab the OTA status handle of function name.
And let's define it up here.
And comment that OTA status handler responds with the firmware update status after the OTA update is
started.
And responds with the compile time.
And date.
When the page is first requested.
And the parameter already, Q, is HTTP requests for which the you are right needs to be handled.
And the return is ESP, OK?
All right.
And this is an ESP type.
And it's our state status handler, which takes the ftpd request type.
Pointer our IQ.
And let's create a care Jason buffer.
With length 100.
And then log that OTA status is requested.
Now we're going to sprint Jeff into what, Jason?
And now just follow me as we enter the Jason Escape sequence that's required.
Just like so and into our OTA update status.
And then continue.
And then into the compile time.
And then next, the compile date.
And then we can close it and then give it the global firmware update status.
And then give it the time definition.
And the date.
And that's it for the Jason.
So now let's set the response type.
For this request as application JSON.
And then we're going to send the response for the request.
From The Sun, and we want Star of the Sun.
And the now just returned ESP, OK?
All right, so here we just updated the Web page with the OTA update status, compile time and compiled
date using the values from here.
So now let's see how this works by going over to James and go to get update status.
Here we need the compile date and time is updated for this latest firmware element date ID, which is
here in the index that HTML.
All right.
And then depending on the OTA update status, we respond with either the reboot timer is started or
the upload error message is shown on the page.
And the reboot time updates with the message here, and the reboot timer is called recursively here,
decorating each time.
All right, so we'll need to configure this timer on the web server side as well.
So let's go back to the FTP server see file.
And at the top of the file.
We can create the ECP 32 timer configuration.
Which is passed to ESP time of create.
And then say, Konst ESP timer, create args type.
And call it firmware update, reset arcs.
And now we need a callback.
Which is our firmware update reset callback
right here.
And then our ARG is now and the dispatch method is ESP timer task.
And the name is firmware update reset.
OK, now, say e-sport, timer, handle, type.
Is firmware update reset?
And next, we need another function, and we'll define another function here.
Which checks the global firmware update status.
Which is this variable right here?
So we're going to check it.
And it creates the firmware update reset timer.
If the global firmware update status is true.
And that will be a static void.
HTTP server.
Firmware update, reset timer.
And it's void.
All right, so say if global firmware update status is OTA update successful?
Then ESG log.
That.
Firmware updates successful.
And then we'll give the Web page a chance to receive and acknowledge back.
And initialize the timer.
Then SPRO, check.
ESP time or create.
And pass a reference to the reset args and a reference to the firmware update reset.
Now we need to espero check.
BSP timer start once.
And pass the firmware update reset and the time in microseconds.
Which we could do maybe eight seconds here.
So we'll say else.
S.P. log.
That the firmware update was unsuccessful.
OK, so now let's grab this function.
And we're going to call it here under the firmware update.
Successful case.
All right.
Next, let's go down.
And we need to define a callback.
So let's take the prototype you.
And then let's drop it right here.
And we'll say ESP log.
That the time or time dealt.
Restarting the device.
All right, then call ESP Restart.
OK, so that looks good.
And one more thing that I forgot here.
And the update was to increment the content received by the body part length.
So let's do that.
Now, let's build the project.
And we had no errors.
Great, so let's test this out in the next lesson.